<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE tudu SYSTEM "/usr/local/share/tudu/tudu.dtd">
<todo>
	<todo done="yes" collapse="no">
		<title>double-width character support</title>
		<text>Japanese language uses many kind characters. Some of them                                                                                                                
like Kanji and Hiragana, occupy double width compared to Alphabet.                                                                                                       
It means simple character count is not enough for correct drawing                                                                                                        
in fixed column width.
</text>
	</todo>
	<todo done="no" collapse="no">
		<title>show category on the tudurc</title>
		<text>I use the commmand :showonly cat1 cat2 to see only this two categories. This works very fine. Is it possible to add this in .tudurc?

Because i use the same .tudu.xml for home and office. And i want only to see office categories on my laptop and only home categories on the privat pc.
</text>
	</todo>
	<todo done="no" collapse="no">
		<title>mark default options in man file</title>
		<text>
</text>
	</todo>
	<todo done="no" collapse="no">
		<title>command line interface for sort order or show info while press b</title>
		<text>
</text>
	</todo>
	<todo done="no" collapse="no">
		<title>one task two places</title>
		<text>
</text>
	</todo>
	<todo done="no" collapse="no">
		<title>cli interface</title>
		<text>
</text>
	</todo>
	<todo done="no" collapse="no">
		<title>cooerent editor and title</title>
		<text>
</text>
	</todo>
	<todo done="no" collapse="no">
		<title>import and export</title>
		<text>
</text>
	</todo>
	<todo done="no" collapse="no">
		<title>more filters (by project, keyword, date)</title>
		<text>
</text>
	</todo>
	<todo done="no" collapse="no">
		<title>more states for a task (undone, done, waiting, maybe, ...)</title>
		<text>
</text>
	</todo>
	<todo done="no" collapse="no">
		<title>dates in human format</title>
		<text>option for entering dates in "human" format like "2d", which will result in deadline date=today+2 days; 3w, 3m and so on.
</text>
	</todo>
	<todo done="no" collapse="no">
		<title>optional navigating throw tree with only "j" and "k"</title>
		<text>option for navigating throw tree with only "j" and "k", so when cursor stands on a level 0 with with sub level, pressing j will lead to changing a cursor position to 0-1, then 0-2 and so on, probably the depth level of such behavior should be adjustable through config file
</text>
	</todo>
	<todo done="no" collapse="no">
		<title>time accounting</title>
		<text>How about a feature to log when I had spent time on it in the past, which is sporadic for my long long list of todo's.  Such log can be amusing when looking back a few years down the road -- why did I spent that amount of time doing that !?
 
Taskwarrior has some thoughts on it
http://taskwarrior.org/boards/6/topics/79


Una de las prestaciones que no he encontrado en otros programas de gestión de tareas es sobre la duración de las tareas, poder decir el tiempo estimado que requiero para cada tarea, y que me avise si me saturo.

En la versión en papel que empecé a usar (sin continuidad) solía poner la duración estimada de la tarea, pero claro el papel no me hacía la suma.

Lo más interesante que encontré fuen en Lightning ó Mozilla Sunbird, donde en la agenda-calendario te marca los días en los que tienes tareas pendientes creo recordar. Además se puede poner el % que has realizado, y no recuerdo si también la duración estimada de cada tarea, pero cada dato se trata por separado, no se usa para facilitar la gestión del tiempo que es necesario reservar para las tareas. Es decir, sabiendo que para dentro de 2 días tengo que hacer 5 tareas que me llevaran Xi.%i tiempo en total, puedo saber si me va a dar tiempo ó no. En Lightning tienes la agenda, gestionas que no se solapen las citas, pero si en los huecos ocupados tienes tiempo justo para las tareas pendientes también debería ser razón para no poner una cita nueva.

Pues eso, que podría ser una feature para TuDu que te avise de que el día tiene 24 horas (ó útiles para hacer tareas menos).
</text>
	</todo>
	<todo done="no" collapse="no">
		<title>deadline and scheduler with hour</title>
		<text>La fecha de fin es solo fecha, por lo que veo no se puede poner también la hora. ¿ó se puede configurar que si?
</text>
	</todo>
</todo>
