<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE tudu SYSTEM "/usr/local/share/tudu/tudu.dtd">
<todo>
	<todo done="no" collapse="no">
		<title>command line interface for sort order or show info while press b</title>
		<text>
</text>
	</todo>
	<todo done="no" collapse="no">
		<title>one task two places</title>
		<text>
</text>
	</todo>
	<todo done="no" collapse="no">
		<title>cli interface</title>
		<text>
</text>
	</todo>
	<todo done="no" collapse="no">
		<title>cooerent editor and title</title>
		<text>
</text>
	</todo>
	<todo done="no" collapse="no">
		<title>import and export</title>
		<text>
</text>
	</todo>
	<todo done="no" collapse="no">
		<title>more filters (by project, keyword, date)</title>
		<text>
</text>
	</todo>
	<todo done="no" collapse="no">
		<title>more states for a task (undone, done, waiting, maybe, ...)</title>
		<text>
</text>
	</todo>
	<todo done="no" collapse="no">
		<title>configure the tudu.xml to load</title>
		<text>On 10:56, Thu 25 Mar 10, Ioan Calin Borcoman wrote:
&gt; One more thing - would it be hard for tudu to do something like git?
&gt; That is, if there is a .tudu xml file in the current dir or one of the
&gt; parent dirs, load it by default? This way, I could keep my todo for my
&gt; app with the code, on my repository. It's not a big deal, as tudu -f
&gt; tudu.xml is not that complicated, but I think it could be nice.

Maybe with an env variable like TUDU_XML, if is not set tudu read your
$HOME/.tudu.xml if is set tudu reads the file on it. So you can set in
your .profile:
export TUDU_XML=.tudu.xml

But in this case I'm not sure what to do if the $TUDU_XML file don't exist.
Should I create it? I think the answer is yes, but in your case could not be
what you wanted.

I'll think about it. Could be a nice feature.
</text>
	</todo>
	<todo done="no" collapse="no">
		<title>on done-undone it plots wrong the screen</title>
		<text>
</text>
	</todo>
	<todo done="no" collapse="no">
		<title>tudu -h gives config error, it should not check the config</title>
		<text>
</text>
	</todo>
	<todo done="no" collapse="no">
		<title>dates in human format</title>
		<text>option for entering dates in "human" format like "2d", which will result in deadline date=today+2 days; 3w, 3m and so on.
</text>
	</todo>
	<todo done="no" collapse="no">
		<title>optional navigating throw tree with only "j" and "k"</title>
		<text>option for navigating throw tree with only "j" and "k", so when cursor stands on a level 0 with with sub level, pressing j will lead to changing a cursor position to 0-1, then 0-2 and so on, probably the depth level of such behavior should be adjustable through config file
</text>
	</todo>
	<todo done="no" collapse="no">
		<title>mark default options in man file</title>
		<text>
</text>
	</todo>
	<todo done="yes" collapse="no">
		<title>support for non-latin keybindings pairs</title>
		<text>support for non-latin keybindings pairs, ideally we should have a table of them, so when I use, for example, russian keyboard layout, I don't need to switch to english layout for operating tudu
</text>
	</todo>
	<todo done="yes" collapse="no">
		<title>arrows on date editor</title>
		<text>
</text>
	</todo>
	<todo done="yes" collapse="no">
		<title>freeze moving task</title>
		<text>Program freezes and doesn't respond even to C-c
ubuntu 10.10 32-bit with almost standard configuration with tudu 0.8;

reproduce:
make a list with such an hierarchy:
 1
 -1.1
 -1.2
Then try to move 1.2 down, this will result in program freeze
</text>
	</todo>
	<todo done="yes" collapse="no">
		<title>fix debian bug #611077</title>
		<text>
</text>
	</todo>
</todo>
